aaptiv.com 2017-03-05

# Privacy Policy

**Aaptiv Inc. Privacy Policy**

**Updated September 27** **, 2016**

This Privacy Policy (“Policy”) provides information about the information that Aaptiv Inc. (“Aaptiv” or “We”) may collect from users of our website (the “Site”) and/or our mobile application (the "App") and how we use and share such information. By using the Site or the App, you agree to the terms of this Policy. We may change this Policy from time to time, and changes are effective upon posting. Please review our Privacy Policy regularly. Your continued use of Aaptiv after changes are posted constitutes your agreement to the changes. If you do not agree to the terms of this Policy, please discontinue your use of the Site and/or App.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing Practices**

Each time you provide or transmit information to us via the Site or App, Aaptiv may obtain and collect personally identifiable information about you, including, but not limited to, your name, email address, and any other information that may be used to identify you.  For example, and without limitation, we may collect such information from you when you create a user account on the Site or App or when you contact our staff.  We may also collect non-personally identifiable information from you.  Non-personally identifiable information is data that is not used to specifically identify, contact, or locate an individual, including but not limited to zip code, gender, age, or IP address.

When you use our Site or App, we may track information regarding your use of our Site or App, including but not limited to, which classes you have taken and timestamps associated with your use of our services.  We may also collect information about your Internet address, browser type, cookie identifiers, Internet Service Provider, referring and exit page, operating system, timestamps, clickstream data, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device’s unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, and your mobile operating system.  We also track and analyze non-identifying and aggregate usage and volume statistical information from our visitors and customers.  We may log and use this information for purposes such as helping diagnose technical problems and to administer our Site or App so that we can improve it.

We may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: (1) to fulfill your requests for classes or other products or services; (2) to respond to your inquiries; (3) to review Site or App usage and operations; (4) to address problems with the Site or App, our business, or our services; (5) to protect the security or integrity of the Site or App and our business; (6) to monitor the Site and App for compliance with our Terms of Use and the law; (7) to help improve our Site, App, or services; and (8) to contact you with updates and other informational and promotional materials from us or third party marketing offers from our trusted partners, as well as from other companies.  In addition, Aaptiv may partner with third party advertisers to help deliver advertisements through the Site or App relevant to your interests. 

We may disclose information collected from and about you as follows: (1) to our related companies and service providers, to perform a business, professional or technical support function for us; (2) to our marketing partners, advertisers or other third parties, who may contact you with their own offers; (3) as necessary if we believe that there has been a violation of our Terms of Use or of our rights or the rights of any third party; (4) to respond to legal process (such as a search warrant, subpoena or court order) and provide information to law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law, or otherwise as required by law; and (5) in the event that our company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, your personal information may be one of the transferred assets. We may also disclose your personal information with your express consent.  We may share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about Website users with third parties.

**Apple HealthKit Information**

In order to provide our services, such as recommending classes you may enjoy, we may read and/or write data to the Apple HealthKit database on your Apple device with your consent. We will not use this information for marketing or advertising purposes or share it with third parties.

**California Privacy Rights**

Under California's "Shine the Light" law, we provide a method for consumers to "opt-out" of having their information shared with third-parties. Contact us at help@aaptiv.com to unsubscribe.

**Interest-Based Advertising**

We may partner with ad networks and other ad serving providers (“Advertising Providers”) who serve ads on behalf of us and others on non-affiliated websites or mobile applications. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information Advertising Providers collect about your visits to this site and elsewhere over time. 

You may visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn more about this type of advertising and how to opt-out of this form of advertising by companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) self-regulatory program.  Note that electing to opt-out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications.  It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests.  In addition, note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

**Children**

Our Site, App, and services are not directed to children under 13. We will never knowingly collect any personally identifiable information about children under the age of 13. If Aaptiv obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted and will not be shared or disclosed to third parties.

**Security**

We maintain reasonable and appropriate measures designed to maintain information we collect in a secure manner.  We have taken certain physical, electronic, and administrative steps to safeguard and secure the information we collect from Site visitors and App users.  Even though we follow reasonable procedures to try to protect the information in our possession, no security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions regarding our Policy, contact us help@aaptiv.com.  If we need, or are required to, contact you for any reason involving your personal information, we may do so by phone, email, or mail.
